<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rasmus Nuko</title>
    <link>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rasmus Nuko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 13:53:27 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rasmusnuko.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 15:09:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you find something I&amp;rsquo;ve made interesting or want to colaborate in some way, feel free to reach out via E-mail rnukoj@gmail.com or LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:19:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Rasmus Nuko Jørgensen and I&amp;rsquo;m based in Denmark. I graduated a B.Sc. in Computer Science from The University of Southern Denmark Odense in 2022. I&amp;rsquo;m currently persuing a Masters degree in Sound and Music Computing at Aalborg University in Copenhagen (2022-2024).
I went with Sound and Music Computing, as it combines two of my interests: Sound and Computing. My musical experience consists of fooling around in Ableton, and not of any traditional training / music education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhISM Percussion Synth</title>
      <link>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/posts/phism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 13:53:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rasmusnuko.github.io/posts/phism/</guid>
      <description>Intention Link to heading This blog post will show the development process of a percussive real time synth.
Prior research Link to heading After telling my supervisors I wanted to build a percussive NIME, one of them suggested I looked at the article Physically Informed Sonic Modeling (PhISM): Synthesis of Percussive Sounds by Perry Cook from 1997.
One-pager containing initial first sketch of NIME and answers to some guiding quetions can be seen in this PDF document.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
